360training.com 2012-11-06

# Website Privacy Policy for 360Training.com

**360training.com Online Privacy Policy** |    
---|---  
  
360training.com respects your privacy. We are committed to protecting your privacy and committed to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. Billing and personal information is encrypted whenever transmitted or received online. Personal information is accessible only to staff, agents, or contractors of 360training. To protect the security of information supplied, all employees and businesses are provided user names and passwords to access their information. 

This privacy statement applies to all 360training.com-owned web sites and domains. This privacy statement covers personally identifiable information, anonymous data collection and aggregate reporting. Personally identifiable information is any information that is associated with your name or personal identity.

**What we collect**  
During the registration process, the types of personal information you provide to us may include, name, address, phone, fax, email address, social security number, license number, date of birth, username and password, billing information, transaction, and credit card information. 

When you browse our web site, you do so anonymously. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our web site you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged in to our web site. Like many other commercial web sites, the 360training web site may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the site. Please go to "Use of Cookies" below for more information. 

**How we use it**  
We use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once.
  * To deliver services that you request or purchase. 
  * To help you effectively complete your educational requirements. 
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you. 
  * To alert you of product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services provided from 360training. 
  * To provide feedback in an online survey. 
  * To participate in promotional offers.
  * To request assistance or fill out support requests. 

**Who we share it with**  
We never sell or rent your personal information. 360training.com may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law (for example, a subpoena)or regulation, or in good faith to **(a)** comply with legal processes served on the site, or **(b)** protect the rights and property of 360training, or **(c)** where our records indicate fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of, or **(d)** where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

When you register, 360training.com will not share your information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above. We use personal information to reply to inquires, handle complaints, provide operational notices, keep records up to date to notify you via periodic e-mails of technical service issues, specials, or other related product/service information. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of 360training for the purpose of performing service for 360training.com. 

**Internet Commerce**  
The online registration at 360training.com is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail and any other information you provide us. 360training is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our site. We offer the industry standard security measures available through your browser called SSL encryption. If at any time you would like to make a purchase, but do not want to provide you credit card information online, you may contact a customer service representative over the telephone. Simply call 1 (800) 442-1149. 

**  
Security of your Personal Information**  
360training.com strictly protects the security of your personal information. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your username and password, so do not share these with others.

We use SSL encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card and personal information. Credit card numbers are only used for processing payment and are not used for other purposes. Our efforts to protect credit card fraud help protect your financial data security. As part of real-time payment processing, 360training.com subscribes to a fraud management service. This service gives both you and 360training.com an extra level of protection to guard against credit card fraud.

**Access to your Personal Information**  
We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time by logging into your account. You can: 

  * View and edit personal information you have already given us.
  * Register and resume courses, curriculum and obtain product updates. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as password and username, before granting access to your data. 

**Use of Cookies**  
Our web sites are not setup to track, collect or distribute personal information. Our site does generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes only. The statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

360training.comWeb sites use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the 360training.com services or Web sites you visit. 

**Problems or complaints with 360training.com Privacy Policy**  
We value your comments and opinions. If you have a questions, comments or a complaint about compliance with this privacy policy you may contact us at [privacy@360training.com](mailto:privacy@360training.com).
